# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the bin/rails db:seed command (or created alongside the database with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   movies = Movie.create([{ name: "Star Wars" }, { name: "Lord of the Rings" }])
#   Character.create(name: "Luke", movie: movies.first)

Stage.create(lesson_id: 1, question: 'Hola', answer: 'Hello')
Stage.create(lesson_id: 1, question: 'Adiós', answer: 'Goodbye')
Stage.create(lesson_id: 1, question: 'Por favor', answer: 'Please')
Stage.create(lesson_id: 1, question: 'Gracias', answer: 'Thank you')
Stage.create(lesson_id: 1, question: 'Lo siento', answer: 'Sorry')
Stage.create(lesson_id: 1, question: 'Buenos días', answer: 'Good morning')
Stage.create(lesson_id: 1, question: 'Buenas tardes', answer: 'Good afternoon')
Stage.create(lesson_id: 1, question: 'Buenas noches', answer: 'Good night')
Stage.create(lesson_id: 1, question: '¿Cómo estás?', answer: 'How are you?')
Stage.create(lesson_id: 1, question: '¿Cómo te llamas?', answer: 'What is your name?')